A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Soviet Studies, Record Group 3, Series 6 FA1486
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowship Records - Declinations (Graduate Training, Dissertation, and Postdoctoral Fellowships), 1990-1991, 1993-1995; 3
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Cilem, Samim, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1613)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Clark, Rhonda, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1614)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Clem, James (Alternate 4), 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1615)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Corbesero, Susan, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1616)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Cunningham, Mary, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1617)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Dakin, Mary, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1618)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Day, Andrew, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1619)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Dickey, Stephen, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1620)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Drummond, W. J., 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1621)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Easley, Roxanne, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1622)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Ewing, E. Thomas, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1623)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Field, Deborah Ann, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1624)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Fraunholtz, Peter, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1625)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Gates, Susan, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1626)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Gerber, Theodore, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1627)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Goeringer, Keith, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1628)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Goldschmidt, Paul, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1629)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Gould, Stephany, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1630)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Hahn, Gordon, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1631)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Hale, Henry, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1632)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Hall, Karl, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1633)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Hegarty, Stephen, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1634)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Herrlinger, Kimberly Page, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1635)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Hirsch, Marcus, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1636)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Holtrop, Daniel, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1637)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Hoogenboom, Hilde, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1638)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Hswe, Patricia (Alternate 3), 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1639)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Johns, Andreas, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1640)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Kagan, Frederick, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1641)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Kalinowska-Blackwood, Izabela, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1642)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Katsev, Allison Yenkin, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1643)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Kelly, Mary E., 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1644)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Kettering, Karen, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1645)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Kionka, Riina, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1646)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Kolesnikova, Elena, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1647)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Konecny, Mark, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1648)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Kotler, Igor, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1649")
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Kubicek, Paul, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1650)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Kunkle, Sheila, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1651)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Leonard, Raymond, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1652)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Little, Martha C., 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1653)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Lofgren, Joan, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1654)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Lyday, Corbin, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1655)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Macrae, Craig, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1656)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Maniichuk, Eileen Consey, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 1657)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Martin, Russell, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1658)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - McDowell, Karen Rice, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1659)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - McLellan, Larry (Alternate 2), 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1660)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Micallef, Roberta, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1661)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Nielson, Forrest, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1662)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Ogden, John, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1663)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - O'Neill, Craig, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1664)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Ostrow, Joel, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1665)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Pinnow, Kenneth, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1666)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Poole, Randall, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1667)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Poulin, Francis, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1668)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Putney, Christopher, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1669)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Pyle, Emily, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1670)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Pyle, William, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1671)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Rapp, Stephen, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1672)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Richmond, Steven, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1673)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Rossman, Jeffrey, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1674)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Schrader, Abby, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1675)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Smith, Douglas, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1676)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Smith, Susannah, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1677)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Snow, Frederick, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1678)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Solomon, Howard, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1679)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Spaeder, David, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1680)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Taylor, Brian, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1681)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Trigos, Ludmilla, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1682)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Wanner, Catherine, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1683)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Wolfe, Thomas, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1684)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Zanca, Russell, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1685)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Baldwin, Kate, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1686)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Castellano, Charlene, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1687)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Christensen, Paul, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1688)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Cienki, Alan, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1689)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Easter, Gerald, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1690)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Economakis, Evel, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1691)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Evdokimova, Svetlana, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1692)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Goldgeier, James, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1693)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Gordon, Ellen J., 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1694)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Granville, Johanna, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1695)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Hickey, Martha Weitzel, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1696)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Hoffmann, David, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1697)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Jeffries, Christopher, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1698)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Jersild, Austin, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1699)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - King, Tracy Holloway, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1700)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Kizenko, Nadieszda (Alternate 2), 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1701)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Krueger, Gary (Alternate 4), 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1702)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Lahti, Katherine, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1703)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Lerner, Valery, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1704)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Martinsen, Deborah Anne, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1705)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Mixter, Timothy, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1706)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Reviewer Comments, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1686 A - 1706 A)
    Reviewer comments separated from individual applicant files (Baldwin - Mixter), in folders 1686-1706.
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Nadkarni, Vidya, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1707)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Nash, David T., 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1708)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Nesbet, Anne, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1709)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Petrone, Karen (Alternate 3), 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1710)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Platt, Kevin, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1711)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Porter, Thomas, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1712)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Roberts, Bryan, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1713)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Ruder, Cynthia, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1714)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Shlapentokh, Dmitry, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1715)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Stanfield, Rosemary, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1716)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Straus, Kenneth, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1717)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Wachtel, Michael, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1718)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Reviewer Comments, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1707 A - 1718 A)
    Reviewer comments separated from folders 1707-1718 (individual files for Nadkarni, Nash, Nesbet, Petrone, Platt, Porter, Roberts, Ruder, Shlapentokh, Stanfield, Straus, and Wachtel).
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Anderson, Gregory David Shelton, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 1719)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Birgerson, Susanne M., 1995 (Box 108, Folder 1720)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Bloom, Stephen, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 1721)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Cavanaugh, Cassandra (Alternate 2), 1995 (Box 108, Folder 1722)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Cheren, Diana Leslie, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 1723)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Conrad, Jo Ann, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 1724)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Coyle, Maria Kardamaki, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 1725)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Eliades, George C., 1995 (Box 108, Folder 1726)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Gaffney, Brendan R., 1995 (Box 108, Folder 1727)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Heron, Lena, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 1728)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Herrera, Yoshiko M., 1995 (Box 108, Folder 1729)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Hyde, Katherine A., 1995 (Box 108, Folder 1730)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Ishkanian, Armine, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1731)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Kasbarian, John Antranig, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1732)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Kassof, Brian, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1733)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Koldys, Gregory, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1734)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Kominiak, Tara A., 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1735)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Kowalsky, Daniel, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1736)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Langen, Timothy Colin, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1737)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Little, Martha Cortelyou, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1738)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - McMahon, Patrice C., 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1739)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - McMann, Kelly Marie, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1740)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Oates, Sarah Ann, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1741)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - O'Brien, Michael, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1742)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Owens, Bradley, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1743)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Pollock, Ethan, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1744)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Plaks, Jeffrey, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1745)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Purcell, Alan, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1746)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Ramaley, Paula, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1747)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Rappoport, Philippa E., 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1748)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Richardson, Curtis, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1749)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Roberts, Sean, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1750)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Southworth, Caleb, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1751)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Taubman, Geoffrey L., 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1752)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Way, Lucan Alan, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1753)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Wells, James A., 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1754)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Woodford, Shawn Robert, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1755)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Avens, Oliver, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1756)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Bernstein, Laurie, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1757)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Carleton, Gregory, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1758)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Reviewer Comments, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1756 A - 1758 A)
    Reviewer comments separated from folders 1756-1758, for Oliver Avens, Laurie Bernstein, and Gregory Carlton.
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Castellano, Charlene, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1759)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Checkel, Jeffrey, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1760)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Christoffersen, Gaye, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1761)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Comer, William, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1762)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Creuziger, Clementine, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1763)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - David-Fox, Michael, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1764)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Easter, Gerald, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1765)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Evdokimova, Svetlana, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1766)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Evtuhov, Catherine, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1767)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Gorham, MIchael, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1768)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Harrison, Richard, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1769)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Hickey, Martha, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1770)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Hoffmann, David, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1771)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Horowitz, Brian, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1772)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Kangas, Roger, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1773)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Kerans, David (Alternate 2), 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1774)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - King, Tracy Holloway, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1775)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Kreuger, Gary, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1776)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Mandel, Ruth, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1777)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Martinsen, Deborah (NEH), 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1778)
    Martinsen's application was forwarded to a Council-wide postdoctoral competition funded by the National Endowment of the Humanities.
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Nelson, Amy, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1779)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Reviewer Comments, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1759 A - 1779 A)
    Reviewer comments separated from individual applicant files (C-N), from folders 1759-1779.
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Petrone, Karen (Alternate 3), 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1780)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Platt, Kevin, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1781)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Schindler, Deborah, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1782)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Shlapentokh, Dmitry, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1783)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Smith, Kathleen E., 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1784)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Valentino, Russell, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1785)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Walker, Barbara, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1786)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Wood, Elizabeth, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1787)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Reviewer Comments, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1780 A - 1787 A)
    Reviewer comments removed from folders 1780-1787, for Petrone, Platt, Schindler, Shlapentokh, Smith, Valentino, Walker, and Wood.
- JCSSS (Joint Committee on the Soviet Union and Its Successor States) and Eurasian Program, 1972, 1980-1996; 4
  The JCSSS and Eurasian Program subseries reflects various ways the SSRC reoriented its Soviet Studies program following the collapse of the Soviet Union in the early 1990s. Materials concern fellowships, workshops, and conferences addressing social, political, and economic changes in the post-Soviet world and in its academic study. The subseries includes early conferences on Soviet Studies and a series of workshops, 1991-1994, reconsidering the History of Imperial Russia. Other materials relate to the SSRC's review of its international programs and area committee structures, particularly in relation to Soviet Studies and the former Soviet Union. Several files pertaining to Title VIII funding and support for Soviet Studies, 1982-1995, are also found in this subseries. Other materials concern programs and fellowships designed to strengthen social sciences in former Soviet states and conferences focusing on Central Asia.
  While most of the materials in this subseries date from 1991-1995 and view Soviet Studies as encompassing the Soviet Successor States and sometimes Central Asia, the subseries also includes some files from the mid-1980s - early 1990s that would more properly be filed in other subseries in the collection and that may relate directly to other materials in these subseries. There are also a few miscellaneous files arranged at the end of the subseries.
  - JCSSS - Advanced Workshop in Post-Soviet Studies - Anthropological and Sociological Perspectives (Papers), 1993 February 6-10 (Box 113, Folder 1833-1834)
    Washington, DC. Folder 1834 contains two papers that may or may not belong with this workshop: paper by Donald Barr, MD, "The Estonian Medical Profession after Fifty Years of Soviet Domination"; and Marie Westbrook Bream, "Perspectives on Education Reform: Independent Schools in Post-Communist Russia, A Case Study."
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology (Papers), 1993 June 19-25 (Box 113, Folder 1835-1837)
  - JCSSS - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology (Papers), 1995 June 24 - July 1 (Box 114, Folder 1838-1839)
  - JCSS - Working Group on Contemporary Soviet Culture - Papers, 1990 June 25-29 (Box 114, Folder 1840)
    Meeting in Moscow. of International Working Group.
  - JCSSS - Working Group on Contemporary Russian Culture - Conference Planning and Report, 1993 July 5-9 (Box 114, Folder 1841)
    Fourth Meeting, London, on "Russian Culture / Soviet Hieroglyphics."
  - JCSSS - Working Group on Contemporary Russian Culture - Papers, 1993 July 5-9 (Box 114, Folder 1842)
  - JCSSS - Proposal for Workshops on Economics of Transition in the Post-Communist World, 1992 (Box 114, Folder 1843)
    Proposals and funding inquiries, for summer workshops in 1993-1994.
  - JCSSS - Workshops on Post-Soviet Politics and on Transition Economics - Funding Inquiries, 1992-1994 (Box 114, Folder 1844)
  - JCSSS - Workshops on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics and on Transition Economics - MacArthur Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 114, Folder 1845)
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Ford Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 114, Folder 1846)
    Ford Foundation grant for Seventh Summer Workshop (Toronto), 1994 June 5-17
  - JCSSS - Workshops on Post-Soviet Politics and Society - ARD and Checchi (Rule of Law Program), 1994 (Box 114, Folder 1847)
    Funding inquiry to Associates in Rural Development (ARD) and Checchi and Co. Consulting, for 1995-1996 workshops in Russia.
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Post-Soviet Politics and Society - Russian Science Foundation Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 114, Folder 1848)
    Planning for summer politics and economics workshops in Moscow for 1995 and 1996.
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Papers, 1995 July 2-14 (Box 115, Folder 1849-1850)
    Workshop in St. Petersburg. Also includes list of workshop applicants from outside the former Soviet Union.
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Course-Pack Materials, 1995 July (Box 115, Folder 1851-1852)
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Additional Faculty Materials, 1995 July 2-14 (Box 132, Folder 2083)
    St. Petersburg. Papers and articles in English and Russian. Includes papers by Valerie Bunce and Bakhtior Islamov, among others.
  - JCSS - Workshop on Reconstructing the History of Imperial Russia - Proposal, Notes, and Reports, 1991 November 1-3 (Box 115, Folder 1853)
  - JCSS - Workshop on Reconstructing the History of Imperial Russia - Planning, 1991 November 1-3 (Box 115, Folder 1854)
  - JCSS - Workshop on Reconstructing the History of Imperial Russia - Papers, 1991 November 1-3 (Box 115, Folder 1855)
  - JCSS - Workshop on Reconstructing the History of Imperial Russia - Responses, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 1856)
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (1) - Schedule and Program Planning, 1993 September 9-12 (Box 115, Folder 1858)
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (1) - Invitations and Responses, 1993 September 9-12 (Box 116, Folder 1859)
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (1) - Participant List and Correspondence, 1993 September 9-12 (Box 116, Folder 1860)
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (1) - Papers, 1993 September 9-12 (Box 116, Folder 1861-1865)
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (1) - Notes on Workshop 1 (Jane Burbank) and Minutes, 1993 September 9-12 (Box 116, Folder 1866)
    Draft minutes of Workshop 1 are unattributed.
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (Workshop 2) - Schedule, 1994 September 22-25 (Box 116, Folder 1867)
    Workshop 2, Portland State University. "Visions, Institutions, and Experiences of Imperial Russia."
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (2) - Invitations, 1994 September 22-25 (Box 116, Folder 1868)
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (2) - Participant List, Correspondence, and Memos, 1994 September 22-25 (Box 116, Folder 1869)
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (2) - Organization and Planning, 1994 September 22-25 (Box 116, Folder 1870)
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (2) - Papers, 1994 September 22-25 (Box 117, Folder 1871-1874)
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (2) - Distribution of Papers, 1994 September 22-25 (Box 117, Folder 1875)